Long time no see, An Qiu
오랜만이에요, 안치우
How do you know who I am?
내가 누구인지 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
because
왜냐하면
I'm your partner
나는 당신의 파트너입니다
What does it mean
무슨 뜻이에요
shanty town
판자촌
We were arrested together
우리는 함께 체포됐다
Run
달리다
Bright-eyed people are here
눈이 밝은 사람들이 여기 있어요
Don't move, let me go
움직이지 마, 날 놔줘
I'm waiting
나는 기다리고있다
noon the day after tomorrow
내일 모레 정오
See you at the same place
같은 곳에서 만나요
If you want to know all the answers
모든 답을 알고 싶다면
chew
씹다
morning
아침
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Why did you want to kill Qin Xinhui?
왜 진신회를 죽이고 싶었나요?
exhibit
전시하다
Maybe Lu Yan led us in the wrong direction
어쩌면 Lu Yan이 우리를 잘못된 방향으로 이끌었을 수도 있습니다.
Yin Tianhong’s goal is not the laboratory
Yin Tianhong의 목표는 실험실이 아닙니다.
But the robot
하지만 로봇은
How else could Chen Xinhui explain it?
Chen Xinhui가 달리 어떻게 설명할 수 있을까요?
It has nothing to do with the laboratory
연구실과는 아무 관련이 없습니다.
And Yin Tianhong doesn't know her either
그리고 Yin Tianhong도 그녀를 모릅니다
Maybe it was after Yin Tianhong saw the news
아마도 Yin Tianhong이 뉴스를 본 이후였을 것입니다.
Know that Chen Xinhui is a robot
Chen Xinhui가 로봇이라는 것을 알아두세요
That's why I killed her
그래서 내가 그녀를 죽였어
Then after he killed someone
그러다가 사람을 죽인 후
Why were the bodies taken away?
시신은 왜 수거됐나요?
Arrange like your twin sign
쌍둥이 사인처럼 배열
Simply perverted
단순히 변태
Every crime has its logic
모든 범죄에는 논리가 있다
So the problem is we don't know the logic now
문제는 우리가 지금 논리를 모른다는 것입니다
That's why I'm stuck here
그게 내가 여기에 갇혀 있는 이유야
This is because of Lu Yan
이게 다 루옌 때문이야
We didn't get any professional resume reports at all.
우리는 전문적인 이력서 보고서를 전혀받지 못했습니다.
It only contains the identification information of the test subjects.
테스트 대상자의 식별 정보만 포함되어 있습니다.
what do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
do you know him?
그를 아니?
You will send the next batch of bots for testing
테스트를 위해 다음 배치의 봇을 보냅니다.
What's up with him?
그 사람은 무슨 일이야?
We doubt
우리는 의심한다
All the robots are in the lab
모든 로봇이 연구실에 있다
They were all killed by him
다 그 사람한테 죽임을 당했어요
Who is Yin Tianhong's employer?
Yin Tianhong의 고용주는 누구입니까?
what kind of person is he
그 사람은 어떤 사람이야?
What is primary mania?
원발성 조증이란 무엇입니까?
speak out
크게 말 해주세요
Information about all robots in the lab
연구실의 모든 로봇에 대한 정보
give me everything
나에게 모든 것을 제공
Yes, I gave you everything.
그래요, 나는 당신에게 모든 것을 주었습니다.
are you sure
확실합니까
certainly
틀림없이
let's go
갑시다
chew
씹다
You're acting strange today
너 오늘 이상하게 행동하는구나
When she had just deceived Lu Yan
그녀가 방금 Lu Yan을 속였을 때
I've never seen you so fierce
나는 당신이 그렇게 맹렬한 것을 본 적이 없습니다
I just want to find Yin Tianhong quickly
빨리 Yin Tianhong을 찾고 싶을 뿐이에요
correct
옳은
When did your mother start building the laboratory?
당신의 어머니는 언제부터 실험실을 짓기 시작하셨나요?
Not long after Mingmu was established, she joined
Mingmu가 설립된 지 얼마 지나지 않아 그녀는 합류했습니다.
I've been very busy since then
그 이후로 정말 바빴어요
It seems I'm trying
노력하고 있는 것 같아
she said here
그녀는 여기서 말했다
That was at Dreamland Club
그건 드림랜드 클럽에서였어
dream club
드림클럽
What on earth is this place?
도대체 이곳은 어떤 곳인가요?
I remember before the subpoena was issued.
소환장이 발부되기 전을 기억합니다.
The media has exposed
언론이 노출한
Provided is an interesting android project
흥미로운 안드로이드 프로젝트가 제공됩니다
Should we go there and check it out?
우리 거기 가서 확인해 볼까?
Something must have happened there
거기에 무슨 일이 있었나 봐요
Who are you?
누구세요?
Who are you
누구세요
I'm a temporary cleaner
나는 임시 청소부야
welcome
환영
We are sharp-eyed investigators
우리는 예리한 조사관이다
Is this the Dreamland Club?
여기가 드림랜드 클럽인가요?
We are investigating the case
우리는 사건을 조사하고 있습니다
Can you take us there?
우리를 그곳으로 데려갈 수 있나요?
he goes
그는 간다
This has been closed for a long time
이곳은 오랫동안 폐쇄되어 있었습니다
what are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
When I close this
내가 이것을 닫을 때
Will it always be empty?
항상 비어있을까요?
After what happened, they all ran away.
그 일이 있은 후 그들은 모두 도망갔습니다.
No one cares anymore
더 이상 아무도 신경 쓰지 않아
everyone ran away
다들 도망갔어
So who will take care of you?
그럼 누가 당신을 돌봐줄까요?
This is commissioned by the broker.
이는 브로커가 의뢰한 것입니다.
Let me see you every few days
며칠에 한 번씩 만나자
As long as the house is good
집이 좋으면
You just said something happened here
방금 여기서 무슨 일이 일어났다고 했죠?
What happened that year?
그 해에 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Have you heard of Dreamland Club?
드림랜드 클럽에 대해 들어보셨나요?
we only know
우리만 아는
The following are the functions of Android system
다음은 안드로이드 시스템의 기능입니다
I'm not sure
잘 모르겠어요
before issuing a subpoena
소환장을 발부하기 전에
The owner of this club
이 클럽의 주인
Looking for a fleet of robot receptionists
로봇 접수원을 찾고 있습니다.
This is a regular club during the day
낮에는 정규 클럽이에요
Night comes
밤이 온다
So the receptionist was replaced by a robot.
그래서 접수원은 로봇으로 대체되었습니다.
Android later became known as
나중에 Android로 알려지게 되었습니다.
Android receptionists are becoming less common
Android 접수원이 점점 줄어들고 있습니다.
I didn't expect anyone to come here looking for updates.
나는 누군가가 업데이트를 찾으러 여기에 올 것이라고는 기대하지 않았습니다.
On the contrary, more and more
오히려 점점 더
What types of services are provided?
어떤 종류의 서비스가 제공되나요?
how could I know
내가 어떻게 알아
I'm just a cleaner
난 그냥 청소부야
here
여기
A woman was stabbed more than a dozen times
한 여성이 수십 차례 칼에 찔렸다.
Bodies were dumped here.
여기에 시체가 버려졌습니다.
Is she also a guest at the club?
그 사람도 클럽 손님인가요?
What is contact information
연락처란 무엇입니까?
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
You should ask the police about this.
이에 대해서는 경찰에 물어봐야 합니다.
you know where people die
사람들이 어디서 죽는지 알아?
I just don't know her identity
나는 그 사람의 정체를 모른다.
What should be said and what should not be said
해야 할 말과 하지 말아야 할 말
you have a very clear mind
당신은 마음이 아주 맑아요
Have you caught the murderer?
살인자를 잡았나요?
No
아니요
It was later discovered that the deceased was an android.
나중에 밝혀진 바에 따르면 사망자는 안드로이드였습니다.
The case is over
사건은 끝났다
Android
기계적 인조 인간
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
This should be your twins horoscope
이것이 당신의 쌍둥이 별자리여야 합니다
ritual murder
의식적 살인
maybe start from here
어쩌면 여기서부터 시작해볼까
But I always feel like something is missing
하지만 항상 뭔가 부족한 느낌이 들어요
something is missing
무언가가 빠졌어
cluster
무리
exhibit
전시하다
when the murder occurred
살인이 일어났을 때
Yin Tianhong should be there too
Yin Tianhong도 거기 있어야 해
This is the address Sister Qiao told you
차오 자매님이 알려준 주소입니다
correct
옳은
How does she know everything?
그녀는 어떻게 모든 것을 알고 있습니까?
That's it
그게 다야
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
Sister Gu sent photos of death at the scene
구자매가 현장에서 사망한 사진을 보냈다
The deceased in Dream Club was named Luo Su
드림클럽 고인의 이름은 루오쑤(Luo Su)
The murderer strangled her to death
살인자는 그녀를 목졸라 죽였다.
I have dozens of extra packages
수십 개의 추가 패키지가 있습니다.
This is perverted
이건 변태야
Your name is Tang Min
당신의 이름은 탕민이에요
We are sharp-eyed investigators
우리는 예리한 조사관이다
Dream Club a year ago
드림클럽 1년 전
The robot is dead
로봇이 죽었어
Was it you who went to identify the body?
시신 확인하러 간 게 당신이었나?
Come and drink some water
와서 물 좀 마셔
Thanks
감사해요
excuse me
실례합니다
We are here to ask about Luosu.
우리는 Luosu에 대해 물어보려고 왔습니다.
your house is beautiful
네 집은 아름다워
It is said
라고 한다
I've worked in clubs before.
예전에 클럽에서 일한 적 있어요.
Yes, I used to work as a cashier there.
네, 저는 그곳에서 계산원으로 일했어요.
I heard that you and Luo Su have a good relationship.
당신과 Luo Su가 좋은 관계를 가지고 있다고 들었습니다.
Because these are the guests who come to the club to spend money
클럽에 돈쓰러 오는 손님들이니까
He often bullies others just because he has money.
그는 돈이 있다는 이유만으로 다른 사람을 괴롭히는 경우가 많습니다.
It stops it for me every time
매번 날 멈추게 해
Did you know this is Android?
이것이 안드로이드라는 것을 알고 계셨습니까?
nightclub receptionist
나이트클럽 접수원
They are all Android
그들은 모두 안드로이드입니다
Rossu is also a receptionist
Rossu는 접수원이기도 하다
She was one of the first receptionists
그녀는 최초의 접수원 중 한 명이었습니다.
when i leave
내가 떠날 때
She has been working there for a long time
그녀는 오랫동안 그곳에서 일해 왔습니다
you are in the club
당신은 클럽에 있어요
Have you met this person?
이 사람을 만나본 적 있나요?
He is also the receptionist
그 사람도 접수원이거든
What is his relationship with Luo Su?
Luo Su와의 관계는 무엇입니까?
Both
둘 다
They shouldn't know each other, right?
그들은 서로를 몰라서는 안 됩니다. 그렇죠?
Russell was seriously ill at the time
러셀은 당시 심각한 질병을 앓고 있었습니다.
Then I left the club
그러다가 클럽을 떠났어요
A few months later this guy came
몇 달 뒤에 그 사람이 왔어.
no intersection
교차로 없음
What kind of person is Yin Tianhong?
인텐홍(Yin Tianhong)은 어떤 사람인가요?
this person
이 사람
I'm not very familiar with this.
나는 이것에 대해별로 익숙하지 않습니다.
So why does he want to work at Dreamland Club?
그렇다면 그는 왜 드림랜드 클럽에서 일하고 싶어 하는 걸까요?
Why are you interested in it?
왜 그것에 관심이 있나요?
We have been looking for Yin Tianhong
우리는 Yin Tianhong을 찾고 있었습니다
But found almost nothing
그러나 거의 아무것도 발견되지 않았습니다
any useful information
유용한 정보
I felt a little anxious for a while
한동안 좀 불안한 느낌이 들었어
excuse me
실례합니다
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
Why did he come to the club?
그 사람은 왜 클럽에 왔나요?
Probably because after the subpoena was announced
아마도 소환장이 발표된 이후였을 겁니다.
There are probably a lot of Android devices out there that don’t want to go back.
돌아가고 싶지 않은 Android 기기가 많이 있을 것입니다.
The club is one of the few that can offer robots
클럽은 로봇을 제공할 수 있는 몇 안 되는 클럽 중 하나입니다.
Provide a place to work
일할 수 있는 장소를 제공하라
You just said that Luo Su was sick
방금 Luo Su가 아프다고 했잖아
she has lupus erythematosus
그녀는 홍반성 루푸스를 앓고 있어요
this is very dangerous
이건 매우 위험해요
that's why she is
그래서 그녀는
Expelled from the club
클럽에서 제명됨
So how did she die in the club?
그럼 그녀는 클럽에서 어떻게 죽었나요?
I do not know why either
나도 왜인지는 모르겠어
you never doubted
넌 의심한 적 없어
Who is the murderer?
살인자는 누구입니까?
Of course I also have questions
물론 나에게도 질문이 있다.
But people in the company
그런데 회사 사람들이
I'm worried this will affect the company's work
회사 업무에 영향을 끼칠까 봐 걱정됩니다
Then let's all shut up and stop talking.
그럼 우리 다 닥치고 얘기는 그만하자.
This matter is over.
이 문제는 끝났습니다.
But not long after
하지만 얼마 지나지 않아
Clubs remain closed
클럽은 계속 문을 닫습니다
Since Luo Su was brought to Xiyuan
Luo Su가 Xiyuan에 데려온 이후로
things are not going well
일이 잘 안 되고 있어
to the end
끝까지
He died mysteriously
의문의 죽음을 맞이했습니다
I don't even know why he died.
나는 그가 왜 죽었는지조차 모릅니다.
Yin Tianhong and Luo Su
인텐홍(Yin Tianhong)과 루오수(Luo Su)
It's time to enter the Dreamland Club
이제 드림랜드 클럽에 입장할 시간입니다
No intersection at all
교차로가 전혀 없음
If Yin Tianhong kills her
Yin Tianhong이 그녀를 죽인다면
Why?
왜?
Insufficient motive and insufficient evidence.
동기도 불충분하고 증거도 불충분합니다.
Maybe Rossu
아마도 로수
When I returned to Dreamland Club, I met him by chance.
드림랜드 클럽으로 돌아왔을 때 우연히 그를 만났습니다.
If you only see him occasionally
그 사람을 가끔씩만 만난다면
Why is he a killer?
그는 왜 살인자입니까?
He stabbed him several times
그 사람을 여러 번 찔렀어요
so you think
그래서 당신은 생각
He is not a killer
그는 살인자가 아니다
I just want to
나는 그저 원할 뿐이야
Things may not be as simple as we think
상황은 우리가 생각하는 것만큼 간단하지 않을 수도 있습니다
We were trapped in a shantytown together.
우리는 함께 판자촌에 갇혔습니다.
If you want to know all the answers
모든 답을 알고 싶다면
noon the day after tomorrow
내일 모레 정오
See you at the same place
같은 곳에서 만나요
I know you will definitely come
나는 당신이 반드시 올 것이라는 것을 알고 있습니다
I'm not here for you today
오늘은 널 위해 여기 온 게 아니야
for truth
진실을 위해
those robots
그 로봇들
Did you kill him?
당신이 그를 죽였나요?
Why
왜
save them
그들을 구해줘
Help them get rid of their major problems
그들의 주요 문제를 제거하도록 도와주세요
Stop making excuses for your deviations
일탈에 대해 변명하지 마세요
They don't need you to save them at all
그들은 당신을 구해줄 필요가 전혀 없습니다
Because of her initial obsession, Qin Xinhui
그녀의 초기 집착 때문에 Qin Xinhui는
trying to displace buyers
구매자를 대체하려고
Even her son Fang Yuan
심지어 그녀의 아들 Fang Yuan도
He killed his mother with his own hands
그는 자신의 손으로 어머니를 죽였다
Do you think this is true?
이것이 사실이라고 생각하시나요?
So you killed her
그래서 당신이 그녀를 죽였어
I said that
나는 그렇게 말했다
I save them
나는 그들을 구한다
After killing Li Yi
리이를 죽인 후
I was originally going to leave Xiyuan City
원래는 Xiyuan City를 떠나려고 했어요
but i never thought about it
하지만 난 그것에 대해 생각해 본 적이 없어
I can see you in the hospital
병원에서 볼 수 있어요
You will be our last hope
당신은 우리의 마지막 희망이 될 것입니다
Where is Luosu?
루오쑤는 어디에 있나요?
That's what you do, isn't it?
그게 당신이 하는 일이죠, 그렇죠?
when i was thrown into the club
내가 클럽에 던져졌을 때
It sucked all the blood out of me
그것은 나에게서 모든 피를 빨아들였습니다.
if you really kill me
네가 정말로 나를 죽인다면
Why are you so harsh on her?
왜 그녀에게 그렇게 가혹한가요?
Still need to make up a lot of cuts
아직 컷트가 많이 필요해요
she
그녀
the only person i ever loved
내가 사랑했던 유일한 사람
I don't want that, I don't want that
난 그걸 원하지 않아, 난 그걸 원하지 않아
next person
다음 사람
In no mood
기분이 안 좋아
Come and park your car
와서 차를 주차하세요
Robot trapped in shantytown
판자촌에 갇힌 로봇
All sent to Ming's headquarters
전부 명나라 본부로 보내졌어
but i don't know why
그런데 왜 그런지 모르겠어요
we have a group of people
우리에겐 한 무리의 사람들이 있어요
He was secretly moved to another location
그는 몰래 다른 곳으로 옮겨졌다
Every day people are taken for interrogation
매일 사람들이 심문을 받으러 갑니다
suffer mental torture
정신적 고문을 당하다
I am not immune
나는 면역이 아니다
They often put pressure on me
그들은 종종 나에게 압력을 가한다
Challenging the end result in different ways
다양한 방식으로 최종 결과에 도전
Can you stop asking?
그만 물어봐도 될까요?
They tortured me mentally and physically
그들은 나를 정신적, 육체적으로 고문했어요
Until one day I heard them talking
어느 날 그들이 말하는 것을 듣기 전까지는
Several test subjects have died recently
최근 여러 실험 대상이 사망했습니다.
So what's going on with Ming?
그렇다면 밍에게는 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
The boss said not to worry, he would take care of it.
사장님이 걱정하지 말고 알아서 처리하겠다고 하셨다.
She said her eyes were bright
눈이 반짝반짝 빛난다고 하더군요
Let's trust humanity again
다시 인류를 믿자
In fact, they already have mites in them.
사실, 그 안에는 이미 진드기가 있습니다.
Humans can never be trusted
인간은 절대 믿을 수 없다
Why did you open the door?
왜 문을 열었어요?
I've opened the door
문을 열었어요
Everyone, run quickly
다들 빨리 달려
One night my friend broke the door lock
어느 날 밤 내 친구가 문 잠금 장치를 부수었습니다.
Then we have a chance to escape
그럼 탈출할 기회가 있겠지
After escaping from the underground laboratory
지하 연구실에서 탈출한 후
I've been hiding
나는 숨어 있었어
If this is the case
만일이 경우라면
He was the first person to help me
그 사람이 나를 도와준 첫 번째 사람이었어
It also made me feel the world for the first time
처음으로 세상을 느끼게 해줬어
Someone still cares about me
누군가 여전히 나에게 관심을 갖고 있다
You guessed my identity
넌 내 정체를 짐작했지
She told me she was a robot too
자기도 로봇이라고 하더군요
Enter
입력하다
Sit anywhere
아무데나 앉으세요
What are you avoiding?
당신은 무엇을 피하고 있습니까?
My home is relatively simple
내 집은 비교적 단순하다.
But it's better than living abroad
그래도 외국에서 사는 것보다는 낫지
If you don't mind, just sleep on the sofa.
괜찮다면 그냥 소파에서 자세요.
speak out
크게 말 해주세요
What do you want me to do for you?
내가 당신을 위해 무엇을 해주기를 바라나요?
I ask you to help me wipe my face clean
얼굴을 깨끗이 닦을 수 있게 도와달라고 부탁해요
I spent this moment with you too
나도 너와 함께 이 순간을 보냈어
If only someone had helped me.
누군가 나를 도와줬더라면.
What medicine did you take this time?
이번에는 무슨 약을 드셨나요?
vitamins
비타민
I'm hungry
배고파요
Have a meal
식사하세요
if something happens
무슨 일이 생기면
you must tell me
당신은 나에게 말해야합니다
It's cold whether you eat it or not.
먹든 말든 춥다.
Take medicine to the hospital
약을 가지고 병원에 가세요
Let's go to the hospital to get medicine
약을 받으러 병원에 가자
Come
오다
come drink water
물 마시러 오세요
lupus erythematosus
홍반루푸스
incurable disease
말질
Going to the hospital is a waste of money
병원에 가는 것은 돈 낭비이다
i can find more jobs
더 많은 일자리를 찾을 수 있어요
Now except Dreamland Club
이제 드림랜드 클럽은 제외
Who dares to work for us?
누가 감히 우리를 위해 일하겠습니까?
Look, this idiot is still here.
봐, 이 바보가 아직 여기 있잖아.
Still in love?
여전히 사랑에 빠져있다?
Do you really think of yourself as a person?
당신은 정말로 자신을 사람이라고 생각합니까?
How long have you been waiting for me?
당신은 나를 얼마나 오랫동안 기다리고 있었나요?
this is a love
이건 사랑이야
and gifts
그리고 선물
give it back to me
나한테 돌려줘
oops
이런
Android devices can actually write love letters
안드로이드 기기는 실제로 러브레터를 쓸 수 있다
a love letter
연애 편지
Thoughts for everyone
모두를 위한 생각
Meow meow
야옹 야옹
Received love letter for the first time
처음으로 받은 러브레터
Dear Sue
친애하는 수
Be serious, be serious
진지해, 진지해
You are the first person to be nice to me
나한테 친절하게 대해준 사람은 네가 처음이야
He was also the first person to enter my heart
내 마음에 가장 먼저 들어온 사람이기도 했고
when i write this letter
내가 이 편지를 쓸 때
i fall deeply in love with you
나는 당신과 깊은 사랑에 빠졌습니다
i can do anything for you
나는 당신을 위해 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다
very influential
매우 영향력이 크다
so you think
그래서 당신은 생각
my love for you is real
당신을 향한 나의 사랑은 진짜예요
tear well
잘 찢다
throw it in his face
그의 얼굴에 던져
Do you really think we are in love?
우리가 정말 사랑에 빠졌다고 생각하시나요?
I'm just kidding you
농담이에요
This is our little game in the land of dreams
이건 꿈의 나라에서의 우리의 작은 게임이야
I'll let you go now
이제 널 보내줄게
Never go back to dreamland again
다시는 꿈나라로 돌아가지 마세요
Apparently we are all robots
분명히 우리는 모두 로봇이다
Why do you hurt me more?
왜 나에게 더 상처를 주나요?
but they are of the same type
하지만 그것들은 같은 종류야
i believe everything
나는 모든 것을 믿는다
It’s all because of the initial obsession
다 초기 집착 때문이야
You know what my first obsession was?
내 첫 집착이 뭔지 알아?
I was playing with the boys.
나는 소년들과 놀고 있었다.
I wouldn't change this
나는 이것을 바꾸지 않을 것이다
I'm just tired of playing with you
난 그냥 너랑 노는 게 지쳤어
Do you still want to help me?
아직도 나를 돕고 싶나요?
Please help yourself
스스로 도와주세요
roll
롤
Because of her initial obsession
그녀의 초기 집착 때문에
and kana
그리고 가나
Don't you think so?
그렇게 생각하지 않나요?
Robots are surrounded by primal obsessions
로봇은 원초적인 집착에 둘러싸여 있습니다.
twisted
꼬인
they will hurt others
그들은 다른 사람들에게 상처를 줄 것이다
I can't be myself again
난 다시 나 자신이 될 수 없어
I've given them a chance before
난 전에 그들에게 기회를 준 적이 있어요
But no one can break through his original obsession
하지만 그 누구도 원래의 집착을 깨뜨릴 수는 없다.
I can only save them
난 그들을 구할 수 밖에 없어
I don't know Luo Su
나는 루오수를 모른다
Did I really cheat on you?
내가 정말 당신을 속였나요?
but kill it
하지만 죽여버려
Unable to save
저장할 수 없습니다.
I can't even save you
난 널 구해줄 수도 없어
An Qiu, do you know?
안 치우, 알고 있나요?
You are still the same as before
넌 여전히 예전과 똑같아
very happy
매우 기쁘다
at least i still remember
적어도 난 아직도 기억해
The look in the eyes of the person who hurt me
나에게 상처를 준 사람의 눈빛
but you forgot
하지만 당신은 잊어버렸어요
What does it mean
무슨 뜻이에요
Do you still remember your brother Anyang?
아직도 안양오빠를 기억하시나요?
my brother
내 동생
Open
열려 있는
I'm already in the shanty town
나는 이미 판자촌에 와 있어요
I got to know you and Anyang
너와 안양을 알게 됐어
At that time, your name was not An Qiu.
그 당시 당신의 이름은 안추(An Qiu)가 아니었습니다.
and called Anqing
그리고 안칭(Anqing)이라고 불렀다.
until
~까지
Run
달리다
Someone with bright eyes is coming, hurry up
눈이 밝은 사람이 온다 어서 빨리
You are an infertile couple
당신은 불임 부부입니다
by order
순서대로
What I care about most is loving my family
내가 가장 중요하게 생각하는 것은 가족을 사랑하는 것이다.
Why do you want to arrest me?
왜 나를 체포하려는 걸까요?
do not move
이동하지 않습니다
After the subpoena is issued
소환장이 발부된 후
The couple left you
그 부부가 당신을 떠났어요
So what can you love?
그렇다면 당신은 무엇을 사랑할 수 있습니까?
All that's left is each other.
남은 건 서로뿐이다.
But when that day comes
하지만 그날이 오면
you can't even do that anymore
넌 이제 그런 짓도 못 해
quickly
빠르게
sit
앉다
I ask you to sit down
앉으라고 하세요
Don't run
뛰지 마세요
Come on, run, run
어서, 달려, 달려
Where is my brother?
내 동생은 어디 있어요?
Kraft
크래프트
stop and be honest
그만하고 솔직해지자
Big brother
형
Brother, wake up
형, 일어나요
look at me
날 봐
Big brother
형
who is this
누구세요
who killed him
누가 그를 죽였는가
Cheng Nu
쳉 누
Why should I believe you?
내가 왜 당신을 믿어야합니까?
Is he hiding something from you?
그가 당신에게 뭔가를 숨기고 있는 걸까요?
About raiding shantytowns
판자촌 습격에 대해
chew
씹다
It's okay if you don't believe me
나를 믿지 않아도 괜찮아
But have you ever thought about it?
하지만 그것에 대해 생각해 본 적이 있나요?
Why are your memories fading?
왜 기억이 희미해지는 걸까요?
Why did you come to Mingmu?
왜 민무에 왔나요?
you are a robot
당신은 로봇이다
Do you know what to do now?
이제 무엇을 해야 할지 아시나요?
I can help you
나는 당신을 도울 수 있습니다
Shen Li
션 리
How long have you known An Qiu?
An Qiu를 알고 지낸 지 얼마나 됐나요?
nearly half a year
거의 반년
What's wrong
뭐가 문제 야
You should graduate earlier than her, right?
그 사람보다 일찍 졸업해야지, 그렇지?
Yes
예
How did you two meet?
두 분은 어떻게 만났나요?
We met in a lecture at school
우리는 학교 강의에서 만났어요
Her professional performance is very good
그녀의 전문적인 성과는 매우 좋습니다
I originally planned to stay
원래는 묵으려고 했는데
Psychological clinic training
심리클리닉 훈련
Then Mingmu came
그러다가 밍무가 왔어
cooperation with you
당신과의 협력
Why do you ask this?
왜 이런 걸 물어보나요?
It's okay, let's meet my partner
괜찮아, 내 파트너를 만나자
What was the past like in school?
학교에서의 과거는 어땠나요?
Did I mention that to you?
내가 당신에게 그 얘기를 했나요?
She only said her family was abroad
가족이 해외에 있다고만 하더군요
have nothing to say
할 말이 없다
What happened to An Qiu?
안추에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Suddenly you care about her
갑자기 당신은 그녀에 대해 걱정
That's okay, I still have work to do.
괜찮아요. 아직 할 일이 남아 있어요.
welcome
환영
Please contact me
저에게 연락주세요
Owner WestX00120
소유자 WestX00120
Ask him if he has a rear driving recorder
후방 주행 기록 장치가 있는지 물어보세요.
Where are you
어디세요
at home
집에서
That day in the hospital
그날 병원에서
Have you really never met Yin Tianhong?
정말로 Yin Tianhong을 만난 적이 없나요?
No
아니요